{
    "id": "d8a6313d15ce4904865f12ae638ea3fe",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The kids broke ................................ as soon as they saw the buffoon.",
            "description": "Break up can mean start laughing.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b169664872ab40a389815492a04407b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a mystery how the prisoners managed to break .................................. of jail.",
            "description": "To break out is to escape.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4eb8733ac9ac4773b7c4da06d47c6d85"
        },
        {
            "question": "I broke ......................................... a rash after taking a dip in the pond.",
            "description": "To break out in something is to develop a skin condition.",
            "answers": [
                "out in",
                "out on",
                "up in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "646c3d682ef043ea8ac2f7ef1d4f49e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news of his death brought me .....................................",
            "description": "If something makes you down, it makes you unhappy.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ceb08c7fc9a4863879ed939b9172784"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't like it when you bring ................................................ politics.",
            "description": "To bring a topic up is to start talking about it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d456f0fdec04fbd8633f4989daa9306"
        },
        {
            "question": "I called ...................................... but I could not find anyone to fix the roof.",
            "description": "To call around is to phone many different places / people.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "around"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "168ae227623248638049a81a2e3489ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "He drew a blank when the professor called ........................................ him for question",
            "description": "To call on somebody is to ask for an answer.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df51f9852b1b4a59ade7f52d73db5f20"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I ran faster I couldn't catch ......................................... with her.",
            "description": "To catch up with somebody is to get to the same point as them.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "57191b6512c041b9853dd7cdb8aa064c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The company checks ....................................... all applicants before hiring.",
            "description": "To check somebody out is to investigate them.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3c2bb09091244be28e54f9712c882d5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bought the kids some chocolates to cheer them ..........................................",
            "description": "To cheer somebody up is to make them happy.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e58fea2fcd59447da254b43319c99d4e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has come .......................................... flu.",
            "description": "To come down with something is to become sick.",
            "answers": [
                "down with",
                "down",
                "out with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "452f4cb9a70b4fe9ad41e54e11056577"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you want to lose weight, you have to cut .............................................. sweets and burgers.",
            "description": "To cut back on something is to consume less.",
            "answers": [
                "up on",
                "out on",
                "back on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ff179a48ada3439a869a96f47ae2c60a"
        }
    ]
}